Better-than-Freehold™ offers foreign investors in Thailand a secure
and clear property ownership method.
This innovative approach simplifies the real estate market, providing
a reliable alternative to traditional freehold ownership and
enhancing investment security and returns.
Thailand's economic growth and strategic location in the heart of
south east asia offers long-term capital appreciation.
With approximately 40 million annual tourists, locations like
Bangkok, Phuket, Chiang Mai, and Ko Samui feature
strong rental markets.
Infrastructure investments also boost property values over time,
making Thailand an investment paradise.
For lawyers, Better-than-Freehold offers a secure alternative to
risky nominee arrangements, aligning with Thai law
and international standards.
It ensures client protection and enforceability, complying with the
Foreign Business Act and Land Code, with court-tested contracts and
succession provisions.
Enhance your advisory role by recommending Better-than-Freehold,
showcasing your expertise in property law.
Differentiate your practice with exclusive certification, generate
revenue through implementation and compliance reviews, and build
long-term client relationships with effective property portfolio
management services.
For developers, Better-than-Freehold offers a compliant ownership
structure that ensures due diligence from international banks.
Differentiate your projects with a focus on security, attracting
sophisticated investors from overseas, while commanding higher rates
than standard leaseholds with the ability to finance your project
from BtF's commercial partner network.
Build trust with clients by providing a transparent, legally sound
ownership structure.
Better-than-Freehold ensures higher conversion rates and withstands
scrutiny from regulators and other law agencies.
Enhance resale values and expedite transactions with trusted,
professionally drafted documentation and agreements, creating
long-term value and confidence among discerning buyers.
For property owners, Better-than-Freehold provides full protection
and legal certainty through court-tested documentation, eliminating
nominee vulnerabilities.
A multi-layered security framework safeguards against political
changes, and seamless inheritance planning
facilitates wealth preservation.
Exit strategies are simplified with clear, legally recognised
documentation for future sales.
For buyers, Better-than-Freehold offers a seamless property
investment journey in Thailand.
Choose from BtF-certified properties with pre-vetted legal structures
and conduct due diligence with recognised documentation.
Experience a transparent acquisition process with enhanced ownership
rights and secure ownership, now with financing
options for foreign buyers.
Contact us for a free consultation to assess your Thai property
investment needs.
Attend our educational workshops in Bangkok, Phuket, Pattaya, and Koh
Samui for a deeper understanding of the
Better-than-Freehold structure.
Explore developer partnerships to integrate
Better-than-Freehold into your projects.
Reach us at info@betterthanfreehold.com.